

PROFILE

A highly motivated and dedicated travel consultant in the travel & tourism industry. Technically competent with extensive experience of travel booking systems (Galileo & Amadeus), with proven proficiency in all aspect of travel management. The desire to work with pride and enthusiasm has resulted in delivering exceptionally high service standards. An excellent problem solver and multitasker with the tenacity to provide the customer with the best possible travel package and holiday experience.

CONTACT

PHONE: +264 81 352 4204

EMAIL: tumkuume@gmail.com

HOBBIES

- 1. Meeting new people
- 2. Learning and reading novels
- 3. Exploring
- 4. Playing Netball

Core skills

- 1.Excellent organization skills
- 2. Customer focused
- 3.Confident communicator
- 4.Broad knowledge of the travel industry and customer care 5.Technically competent with

extensive experience of travel booking systems

ALBERTINA TAAPOPI NEPANDO

EDUCATION

International Training College Lingua

2015-2017

Advanced Diploma - NQF Level 6 in Travel and Tourism

Andimba Toivo ya Toivo Senior Secondary School

2012-2013

Grade 12 Certificate (Science field)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Etosha Travel and Tours- Travel Consultant

November 2018- Present

Duties: suggesting suitable travel packages, including Air ticketing, accommodation and transportation, supporting colleagues as and when needed, Administrative support, issuing tickets

Etosha Travel and Tours – Internship as a Trainee Travel Consultant May 2018-October2018

Duties: Creating flight, accommodation quotations, Working effectively within a team environment, supporting colleagues as and when needed, Email marketing

Oshapama Delivery Solutions - Marketer

April 2016-June 2016

Duties: Conducting research and analyzing data to identify and define audiences, Planning and presenting ideas and strategies, Promotional activities, Signing up people to use Oshapama services

Languages: Strong command in the English language, Oshiwambo (native), and speaks Portuguese Basic as a foreign language

Computer Skills: Worked and trained in Microsoft office package and comfortable with internet. Ability to transfers skills.

References

1. Ms. Tshuma Hope- (Lecturer at International Training College Lingua Cell: +264 81 408 3279

2 Ms. Helena Amakali- (Tour Guide at Gondwana Namib-Desert Lodge) Cell: +264 81 699 7771







Namibia Senior Secondary Certificate (Subject Award)

This is to certify that the candidate named below was awarded the following grade(s) for the subject(s) shown in the examination of October/November 2013.

ALBERTINA T NEPANDO

Date of Birth: 25 June 1995

Subject
First Language Oshindonga
Biology
Mathematics
Physical Science
English as a Second Language
Geography
SUBJECTS RECORDED: SIX

Level	Grade
Higher	3(THREE
Ordinary	C(c)
Ordinary	C(c)
Ordinary	D(d)
Ordinary	E(e)
Ordinary	E(e)

Thihena

Permanent Secretary Ministry of Education, Namibia 1. K. Raysianiez

Vice-Chancellor University of Cambridge

in collaboration with

University of Cambridge Local Examinations Syndicate



Candidate Number: NAQ28/0132 Certificate Number: 133734356



International Training College Lingua

It is hereby certified that

MAN POLICE

Albertina T Nepando 9 DEC 2018

Identity Number: 95062500133

Having complied with the requirements of
International Training College Lingua
was awarded the

Diploma in

TRAVEL AND TOURISM (NQF Level 6)

AT A CONGREGATION OF INTERNATIONAL TRAINING COLLEGE LINGUA

on 24 May 2018

N 8h

MBU

Director: Academic Affairs Director: Non Academic Affairs

1- 1º pretth.

Managing Director

WINDHOEK

INTERNATIONAL TRAINING COLLEGE LINGUA

Towards Educational Excellence Reg. No: D/2014/0535 Accreditation No: 000003



STATE OF STREET		ACADEMIC TRANSC	RIPI	
Name	Albei	rtina T. Nepando	Number	LCS0015549TT
Qualific	ation	Diploma in Travel and Tourism Level 6		

Academic Year	2015	Semester	1

Modules	Marks	Remarks	
Tourism Industry 1	84	Distinction	
Computer Studies 1	72	Merit	
English for Tourism Purposes 1	69	Credit	
Ecotourism 1	62	Credit	
Marketing 1	80	Distinction	
Portuguese	75	Distinction	

Academic Year	2015	Semester	2	

Academic Year 2013 Semester 2		
Modules	Marks	Remarks
Customer Services 1	82	Distinction
Developing a Visitor Attract.	78	Distinction
Portuguese	76	Distinction
English for Tourism Purposes 1	73	Merit
Reservation & Ticketing	82	Distinction
Tourism Geography 1	65	Credit
Present Tourism Prod.&Service	88	Distinction
		M. A. A. Direct St. M. A.

Academic Year	2016	Semester	1

Academic Year 2010 Semester 1			THE PERSON ASSESSMENT OF THE PERSON ASSESSMENT
Modules	<u>Marks</u>	Remarks ! &	W/ NUMBERY
Tourism Industry 2	83	Distinction	
People Development	73	Merit /	A 5 Parks
Business Systems	59	Pass	0 9 DEU 2018
Marketing 2	90	Distinction	

Academic Vear	2016	Semester	2

Academic Year 2016 Semester 2		A PARTICULAR DESCRIPTION OF THE PARTY OF THE
Modules	Marks	Remarks REENWELL MATCHGO MORU & STATE
Customer Service 2	84	Distinction
Developing a Tourism Dest.	70	Merit
Related Tourism Services	86	Distinction
Tourism Geography 2	87	Distinction
Tour Guiding Skills	90	Distinction

Academic Year	2017	Semester	1

Modules	Marks	Remarks	
Customer Services 3	75	Distinction	
Mnge Operations & Information	91	Distinction	
Managing People	86	Distinction	

Academic Year	2017	Semester	2

Marks	Remarks
95	Distinction
90	Distinction
91	Distinction
65	Credit
	95 90 91

Grading Scale

0 - 44 = Fail

45 - 49 = Supplementary

50 - 59 = Pass

60 - 69 = Credit

70 - 74 = Merit

75 - 100 = Distinction

Mrs. L. Hartung
Chegked/Verified Head of Non-Academic Affairs

Ms. Kawesha

Checked/Verified Head of Examinations



Object

Certificate of Achievement

AN POLICE MADEUS

.0 9 DEC 2018

This is to certify that

Albertina Nepando

a Beginners Course

Has successfully completed

On

04/06/2018 - 08/06/2018



Amadeus Southern Africa Training Manager



Jacqui Mc Govern

Travelport MyLearning



Certificate of Completion

This is to certify that

Albertina Nepando

has successfully completed

Galileo Core Assessment

Monday, November 12, 2018

Date of Certification

Awarded by **Stephen Shurrock**Chief Commerical Officer

Travelport MyLearning



Certificate of Completion

This is to certify that

Albertina Nepando

has successfully completed

Galileo Expert Course Assessment (Fares and ticketing)

Thursday, November 22, 2018

Date of Certification

Awarded by **Stephen Shurrock**Chief Commerical Officer

Travelport MyLearning



Certificate of Completion

This is to certify that

Albertina Nepando

has successfully completed

Galileo Professional Course Assessment (Hotels, Cars, Client File)

Monday, December 03, 2018

Date of Certification

Awarded by **Stephen Shurrock**Chief Commerical Officer



Tre Office Suites, 3-5 Grimm Street

Windhoek, Namibia Tel: +264 61 236313

Fax: +264 61 236989

Emergency No's: +264 81 2977034

+264 81 3201009

Email: info@etoshatravel.com Website: www.etoshatravel.com

04 October 2018

Internship Testimonial

TO WHOM IT MAY CONCERN

This is to testify that Albertina T. Nepando has been an Intern at Etosha Travel and Tours from 01 April 2018 until 01 October 2018

During this internship period Albertina's main duties were as follow:

- · Determining clients' needs and suggesting suitable travel packages
- Organizing travels from beginning to end, including tickets, accommodation and transportation
- Working effectively within a team environment, supporting colleagues as and when needed
- Administrative support; issuing ticket and e-tickets, issuing refunds, miscellaneous charge orders, dealing with invoices
- Supplying travellers with pertinent information and useful travel/holiday materials

We are very pleased with the outstanding service attitude demonstrated by Albertina. She is very hard working, dedicated to her work, able to work under pressure without much supervision. She is a very responsible and reliable person.

I strongly recommend Ms Albertina T Nepando to any potential employer

Yours Sincerely,

Paulinus Amwele Elago

ETOSHA TRAVEL & TOURS CC PO Box 20118, Windhock 061236313/0812977034 3-5 Grimm Str. Windhoek

info@etoshatravel.com

Travel Consultant Manager

Tel: +264 61 236313 | Fax: +264 61 236989 | Email: info@etoshatravel.com







